David Rockefeller papers, Photographic Collection, Personal, Professional and Travel FA1862
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller papers, Photographic Collection, Personal, Professional and Travel
1920-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
Rockefeller, Peggy
FA1862
17.28 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received. Primarily chronological.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of photographic prints, slides, contact sheets and snapshots, with select negatives.
- Washington - Williamsburg - Pocantico - Seal Harbor - Egypt - England - Scotland - Hong Kong - JY Ranch, 1926-1941 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  This is a general description of all content in the box or set of photographs.
- Western Trip, 1930 (Box 1)
- Florida late 1920s, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
- 1926-1927 (Box 1)
- Western Trip, 1926 (Box 1)
- Trip To France, 1927 (Box 1)
- 1928 (Box 1)
- Trip to England - Scotland, 1932 (Box 1)
- Pocantico, 1933 (Box 1)
- Arizona Summer, 1934 (Box 1)
- Ormand Beach Florida, 1936 (Box 1)
- Peggy Rockefeller and David Rockefeller to Williamsburg, 1941 April (Box 1)
- 1941 April (Box 1)
- Williamsburg, 1941 (Box 1)
- Trip to Williamsburg, 1941 (Box 1)
- 1941 (Box 1)
- 1941 (Box 1)
- Williamsburg VA, 1941 (Box 1)
- 1941 (Box 1)
- 1941 (Box 1)
- Puerto Rico - Blue Ridge Mts - North Africa - France - Mexico - Cuba - South America, 1942-1950 (Box 2)
- Aligers, Morocco, Jerusalem, Jordan, and Egypt, 1943-1944 (Box 2)
- 1943-1944 (Box 2)
- Morocco - South of France, 1944 (Box 2)
- 1944 September-October (Box 2)
- Aligers, 1944 (Box 2)
- 1944 (Box 2)
- Jerusalem Winter, 1944 (Box 2)
- Jerusalem, 1944 (Box 2)
- Mexico, 1946 (Box 2)
- 1946 (Box 2)
- Mexico, 1946 (Box 2)
- 1946 (Box 2)
- Mexico, 1946 (Box 2)
- 1946 (Box 2)
- Seal Harbor California, 1947-1949 (Box 2)
- Cattle Ranch, 1948 (Box 2)
- 1948 (Box 2)
- Quito, Equador, La Paz, Bolivia, 1950 (Box 2)
- 1950 (Box 2)
- Peru Cusco, 1950 (Box 2)
- 1950 (Box 2)
- 1950 (Box 2)
- Honduras - Columbia - Seal Harbor - Middle East - France - England - Spain - Wyoming - St. Barts, 1951-1957 (Box 3)
- Tarrytown; Seal Harbor, 1952 (Box 3)
- Saudia Arabia, 1953 (Box 3)
- Kuwait, 1953 (Box 3)
- Kuwait, Air-view of port and oil facilities, 1953 (Box 3)
- Caribbean Cruise, 1957 (Box 3)
- St. Barts, 1957 (Box 3)
- Granada, 1954 (Box 3)
- Portugal, 1954 (Box 3)
- 1954 (Box 3)
- Spain 1, 1954 (Box 3)
- Spain 2, 1954 (Box 3)
- 1954 (Box 3)
- Spain 3, 1954 (Box 3)
- Florida Keys, 1955 (Box 3)
- Yellowstone Park, 1955 (Box 3)
- Wyoming, 1955 (Box 3)
- Brazil, 1956 (Box 3)
- France; Brazil, 1956 (Box 3)
- Puerto Rico, 1956 (Box 3)
- Hudson Pines; Brazil, 1956 (Box 3)
- AAR Garden, 1950-1960 (Box 3)
- AAR Garden, Seal Harbor, 1930-1931 (Box 3)
- AAR Garden, Seal Harbor (Box 3)
- Early Photos for AAR Garden (Box 3)
- Seal Harbor, 1956 (Box 3)
- St. Barts - Hudson Pines - Peru - Chile - Belgium - Africa, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Box 5)
- Seal Harbor, Late 1950's (Box 4)
- Seal Harbor, 1950 (Box 4)
- On the "Wayfarer", St. Barts, 1958 (Box 4)
- St. Barts (Box 4)
- Belgian Congo; Nigeria; South Africa, 1959 (Box 4)
- Visit on the "Wayfarer", St. Barts, 1958 (Box 4)
- Lagos, Nigeria; Accra, Ghana; Kenya, 1959 (Box 4)
- Nigeria, Kenya, 1959 (Box 4)
- South Africa, Kenyan Park, 1959 (Box 4)
- South Africa, 1959 (Box 4)
- Kenya; Ethiopia - Addis Ababa, 1959 (Box 4)
- Kenya, 1959 (Box 4)
- From a Charter's Cathedral Chateau of the Loire, 1945 (Box 4)
- France, 1945 (Box 4)
- Rhodesia Victoria Falls; Zambezi River; Kenya Treetops; South Africa; Animals in Kenya Park; Capetown, 1959 (Box 4)
- Victoria Falls Zambia-Zimbabwe; South Africa, 1959 (Box 4)
- South Africa, Nigeria, Ghana; Belgian Congo, 1959 (Box 4)
- South Afica, Ghana, Congo, 1959 (Box 4)
- Northern Rhodesia - Victoria Falls; South Africa - Capetown - Beach beyond, 1959 (Box 4)
- South Africa, 1959 (Box 4)
- Accra, Ghana; Belgian Congo (Zaire), 1959 (Box 4)
- Ghana, Congo, 1959 (Box 4)
- Tarrytown, Seal Harbor, Garden at Hudson Pines, Picnic, 1959 (Box 4)
- Seal Harbor, Hudson Pines, 1959 (Box 4)
- Seal Harbor Picnic, 1959 August (Box 4)
- Seal Harbor, 1959 (Box 4)
- Greece, 1959 (Box 4)
- Greece, 1959 (Box 4)
- Greece, 1959 (Box 4)
- Greece, 1959 (Box 4)
- Greece - Mykonos cruising, 1959 (Box 4)
- Stavros, 1959 (Box 5)
- The Wayfarer, Laurance Rockefeller family and David Rockefeller family; Hudson Pines in Winter, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
- 1959-1960 (Box 5)
- Virgin Islands, West Indies, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
- Virgin Islands, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
- JY Ranch - Pack Trip with the Winklers, 1960 (Box 5)
- JY Ranch, 1960 (Box 5)
- Yellowstone Park; JY Ranch Pack Trip with the Winklers, 1960 (Box 5)
- Yellowstone Park, 1960 (Box 5)
- Abby's Graduation at Milton; Barge Trip in France, 1961 (Box 5)
- Visit with Priscilla in Scotland; Barge Trip in France, 1961 (Box 5)
- Scotland; France, 1961 (Box 5)
- Newfoundland on The Wayfarer, 1962 August (Box 5)
- 1962 (Box 5)
- Visit to Nelson's cattle ranch with Dave and Abby; Ciudad Bolivar, Venezuela, 1962 (Box 5)
- Venezuela, 1962 (Box 5)
- Scenes from a plane location, 1962 July (Box 5)
- 1962 July (Box 5)
- Parade in Addis Ababa, Ethiopa; Sudan, 1959 (Box 5)
- Some park outside Nairobi, Kenya; Treetops Addis Ababa, Ethiopia; Sudan, 1959 (Box 5)
- South Africa; Game in Kenyan Park, 1959 (Box 5)
- Ariel view of St. Bart's before the house was built, c. 1959 (Box 5)
- Peru, 1958 (Box 5)
- St. Barts - Before the house was built; Wayfarer, 1958 (Box 5)
- St. Barts - Beginning of work on the house; Wayfarer, 1958 (Box 5)
- British Columbia, The Dangun, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 July (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- The Dangun in British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- B. Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- British Columbia, 1966 (Box 6)
- Canada, 1959 (Box 6)
- Canada, 1959 (Box 6)
- St. Barts, 1960 (Box 6)
- St. Barts, 1960 (Box 6)
- Seal Harbor, 1965 (Box 6)
- S. Harbor, 1965 (Box 6)
- Hudson Pines Garden, 1965 (Box 6)
- Eileen's Graduation, 1965 (Box 6)
- Austrailia; Tahiti (Bora Bora), 1971 (Box 6)
- Tahiti, 1971 (Box 6)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 6)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 6)
- St. Barts, 1973 (Box 6)
- St. Barts, Colombia being built, 1960 (Box 6)
- St. Barts, 1960 (Box 6)
- Beirut; Jeddah; Persephedes (Box 6)
- Beirut, 1962 (Box 6)
- Persephalis, Sofahan, Sheraz (Box 6)
- 1962 (Box 6)
- Sofahan, 1962 (Box 6)
- 1962 (Box 6)
- Sofahan Bangkok, 1962 (Box 7)
- 1962 (Box 7)
- Bangkok; Angkor Wat, Cambodia (Box 7)
- Cambodia, Bangkok, etc., 1962 (Box 7)
- Siem Reap, Cambodia - Angkor Wat, 1962 (Box 7)
- 1962 (Box 7)
- Angkor Wat, Singapore, Manila, Hong Kong (Box 7)
- 1962 (Box 7)
- Kyoto, Fuji, Japan (Box 7)
- 1962 (Box 7)
- Pocantico - Hudson Pines garden in the spring, 1961 May (Box 7)
- Pocantico Hills, 1961 (Box 7)
- Big Sun, California, 1961 (Box 7)
- California, 1961 (Box 7)
- Neva's wedding to Walter Kaiser, 1961 (Box 7)
- Neva's wedding, 1961 (Box 7)
- 1968 (Box 7)
- 1968 (Box 7)
- St. Barts, 1969 (Box 7)
- St. Barts, 1969 (Box 7)
- Seal Harbor, 1969 (Box 7)
- Seal Harbor, 1969 (Box 7)
- Seal Harbor, 1971 (Box 7)
- Seal Harbor, 1971 (Box 7)
- Nepal, 1971 (Box 7)
- Nepal, 1971 (Box 7)
- Nepal, Indonesia, 1971 (Box 7)
- Nepal, 1971 (Box 7)
- Kenya, 1971 (Box 7)
- Kenya, 1971 (Box 7)
- Cambodia, 1962 (Box 7)
- Chile, 1959 (Box 7)
- Big Sur - Hudson Pines - Ringing Point - Seal Harbor - Kenya - Austria - Morocco, 1961-1972 (Box 8, Box 9)
- Visit of President Ahidjo of Cameroon to Pocantico, 1982 (Box 8)
- Kenya, 1971 (Box 8)
- Untitled, 1971 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- Morocco, 1972 (Box 8)
- 1972 (Box 8)
- 1972 (Box 8)
- 1972 (Box 8)
- Arabia, 1972 (Box 8)
- England, 1972 (Box 8)
- 1972 (Box 8)
- England, France, 1972 (Box 8)
- England, 1972 (Box 8)
- President Ahidjo of Cameroon, 1982 (Box 8)
- China, 1982 (Box 8)
- Hudson Pines, King of Morocco, 1982 (Box 8)
- China, 1982 (Box 8)
- Seal Harbor, Douglasses, 1982 (Box 8)
- 1982 (Box 8)
- Liviag top, Tokyo, Hong Kong, 1982 (Box 8)
- Hudson Pines, 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- Seal Harbor, 1982 (Box 9)
- Seal Harbor with the Douglasses, 1982 (Box 9)
- Ringing Point and Cruise, 1982 (Box 9)
- Ringing Point, 1982 (Box 9)
- Chadds Ford, PA, 1982 (Box 9)
- Chad Pond Pepsilwasis, 1982 (Box 9)
- Morocco, 1982 March (Box 9)
- Morocco - Tangiers to Fey, 1982 (Box 9)
- Seal Harbor, Bartlett's Island, 1982 (Box 9)
- Party at Tarrytown for Peggy's Birthday, 1982 (Box 9)
- Guinea, 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- 1982 (Box 9)
- Morocco - Ratt Trip Colorado - Barge - Ireland - France - St. Barts - Pocantico Press Conference, 1983 (Box 10, Box 11)
- St. Barts; Santiago, Chile, 1982 (Box 10)
- St. Barts, 1982 May (Box 10)
- Seal Harbor, 1983 (Box 10)
- 1983 May (Box 10)
- St. Barts, 1983 March (Box 10)
- 2 - Morocco, 1983 (Box 10)
- 3 - Morocco, 1983 (Box 10)
- 4 - Morocco, 1983 (Box 10)
- 2 - Raft Trip on the Colorado River, Utah, 1983 June (Box 10)
- 3 - Raft Trip on the Colorado River, Utah, 1983 June (Box 10)
- 4 - Raft Trip on the Colorado River, Utah, 1983 June (Box 10)
- Colorado River Raft Trip, 1983 June (Box 10)
- France, 1983 July (Box 10)
- France, 1983 (Box 10)
- Carriage Driving - Pocantico; #1 Raft Trip on the Colorado River, Utah, 1983 June (Box 10)
- 5 - Barge Trip in France, 1983 July (Box 10)
- 2 - Canals of France, 1983 July (Box 10)
- 3 - Canals of France, 1983 July (Box 11)
- 4 - Canals of France, 1983 July (Box 11)
- Barge Trip in France - Duplicates, 1983 (Box 11)
- Visit to Ireland, 1983 September (Box 11)
- Morocco; 1 - Canals of France, 1983 July (Box 11)
- Dinner Party, 1983 September 12 (Box 11)
- 1 - Morocco, 1983 (Box 11)
- Thanksgiving on St. Barts, 1986 (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Untitled (Box 11)
- Southeast Asia - St. Barts - Carriage Drive - Australia - Papa New Guinea - Donald's Farewell at Bartletts Island - Kykuit Singing, 1983 (Box 12, Box 13)
- Last trip with Bob Anderson and Bob Douglass (Box 12)
- Untitled, 1984 (Box 12)
- Orleans Farm 1 and 2 (Box 12)
- Orleans Farms (Box 12)
- Portraits on the G-2, #8 (Box 12)
- Thailand - Chiang Mai, Bangkok, 1983 March-April (Box 12)
- Thailand, 1983 (Box 12)
- Chiang Mai, Thailand, 1983 March (Box 12)
- Thailand, 1983 (Box 12)
- Extra photos of S.E. Asia trip, 1983 April (Box 12)
- Asia, 1983 (Box 12)
- N.Y., St. Barts, Seal Harbor, 1983 October-December (Box 12)
- St. Barts,Tarrytown, 1983 (Box 12)
- St. Barts, 1983 March (Box 12)
- Paul and Eileen's pictures, Donald's farewell party on Bartletts Island, 1983 April (Box 12)
- Bartletts Island, 1983 (Box 12)
- Vancouver, Picnics on Bartletts, Napa Valley Cal, St. Barts, 1984 July-August (Box 12)
- Untitled, 1984 (Box 12)
- Jasper Park, Alberta, #3, 1984 July (Box 12)
- Alberta, Canada, 1984 (Box 12)
- Jasper Park, Alberta - glacier, #4, 1984 July (Box 12)
- Canada, 1984 (Box 12)
- Canada, 1984 (Box 12)
- Jasper and Banff Parks, Alberta, #5, 1984 July (Box 12)
- Jasper and Banff Parks, Alberta, 1984 July (Box 12)
- Untitled, 1986 (Box 12)
- GB 09 - Costa Rica - St. Barts - Venezuela - Galapagos Islands - Japan - Bartlett's Island - JY Ranch 45th Anniversary, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Box 14)
- Launching of the Capt. David Bartlett; Weekend at Yosemite Park, Cal, 1984 May (Box 13)
- Main, Yosemite Park, 1984 (Box 13)
- Jasper, Alberta, #6; Simmental cattle at Hudson Pines, 1984 July (Box 13)
- Jasper Park, Hudson Pines, 1984 (Box 13)
- Istanbul, Turkey; Jordan; Pakistan, 1984 February (Box 13)
- Turkey, Jordan, Pakistan, 1984 (Box 13)
- Pakistan, Saudia Arabia, 1984 February (Box 13)
- Pakistan, Saudia Arabia, 1984 (Box 13)
- Weekend at Oppenheimer Park; South Africa, 1984 April (Box 13)
- South Africa, 1984 (Box 13)
- Weekend at Oppenheimer Park; Stellenbosch, South Africa, 1984 April (Box 13)
- South Africa, 1984 (Box 13)
- South Africa- Soweto, Stellenbosch, 1984 April (Box 13)
- Africa, 1984 (Box 13)
- Panama, 1984 October (Box 13)
- Panama, 1984 (Box 13)
- Loose photographs (Box 13)
- Madong, #3 (Box 13)
- Karawari lodge, Papua New Guinea, #4 (Box 13)
- Karawari River, Sepia River, #5 (Box 13)
- Sepia River, #6 (Box 13)
- Calgary stampede and air view of Alberta, #1, 1984 July (Box 13)
- City of Calgary stampede, Alberta, #2, 1984 July (Box 13)
- Launching of Captain David Bartlett, Spring 1984 (Box 13)
- Costa Rica - San Jose, DR giving gold insignia to President Monge, 1984 January (Box 13)
- Trip to Venezuela #1, 1985 February (Box 13)
- Amazonas, Venezuela #2, 1985 February (Box 13)
- Indians of Parima; Amazonas, Venezuela; Galapagos Islands #3, 1985 February (Box 14)
- Galapagos Islands #4, 1985 February (Box 14)
- Galapagos Islands #5, 1985 February (Box 14)
- Galapagos Islands #6, 1985 February (Box 14)
- Galapagos - bird pictures; Chichimeca - Yucatan, Mexico #7, 1985 February (Box 14)
- Chichimeca - Yucatan, Mexico #8, 1985 February (Box 14)
- Japan #1, 1985 April (Box 14)
- Kyoto, Japan #2, 1985 April (Box 14)
- Nana - outdoor sculpture museum, Hakone, Japan #3, 1985 April (Box 14)
- Extras of Marc and Nelson, 1985 August (Box 14)
- Costa Rica, Dick and family, St. Barts, 1984 October-1986 January (Box 14)
- Amazonas territories in Southern Venezuela #3, 1985 February (Box 14)
- France #2, 1985 July (Box 15)
- Strasbourg, France #2, 1985 July (Box 15)
- France and Seal Harbor #3, 1985 July (Box 15)
- Cruise with Nelson and Mark, Seal Harbor, 1985 July (Box 15)
- Our 45th anniversary cruise with all the children, Seal Harbor, 1985 August (Box 15)
- Brazil #2, 1986 January (Box 15)
- Los Angeles, Huntington Gardens, 1986 February (Box 15)
- Argentina, Brazil, Spain, 1986 February (Box 15)
- Huntington Gardens in Pasadena, Cal. #2; Morocco#1, 1986 February (Box 15)
- Morocco #2, 1986 March 2-3 (Box 15)
- Marrakesh, Morocco #3, 25th anniversary coronation of King Hassan II, 1986 March (Box 15)
- Tokyo #1, 1986 March (Box 15)
- Brunei - village; Beijing, 1986 March (Box 15)
- Brunei - palace #2, 1986 March (Box 15)
- China #4 - Lama Temple, free market, Forbidden City, Beijing, 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #5 - Forbidden City, PR at airport, Dagu, 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #6 - Dazu, 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #7 - Dazu, rice fields, Yangtze River trip, 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #8 - Trip on the Daning River (tributary of the Yangtze), 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #9 - Daning River, Yangtze River, 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #10 - Yangtze River, 1986 March (Box 16)
- China #11 - Guilin, 1986 April (Box 16)
- China #12 - Li River at Guilin, 1986 April (Box 16)
- Untitled photographs (Box 16)
- Venezuela #1, 1988 January 13 (Box 17)
- Venezuela #2, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #3, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #4, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela, 1988 (Box 17)
- Venezuela #5, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #7, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #6, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #8, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #9, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #10, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #11, 1988 January (Box 17)
- Venezuela #12, 1988 January (Box 17)
- San Franciso, 1988 February (Box 17)
- Poland, Brazil, 1988 February-March (Box 17)
- Warsaw, Poland, 1988 February (Box 18)
- Brazil, 1988 March (Box 18)
- Brazil #3, 1988 March (Box 18)
- Brazil #4, 1988 March (Box 18)
- Brazil and Paraguay #5, 1988 March (Box 18)
- Paraguay #6, 1988 March (Box 18)
- YPOA - martes 15 marzo 88, 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- Naranja-y - martes 15 marzo 88, 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- Aeropuerto - martes 15 marzo 88, 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- Loma Plata - Chao Paraguayo - martes 15 marzo 88, 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- YPOA - martes 15 marzo 88 (Fotos de Miguel Angel Manzoni), 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- Estudio de la Senora Marta de Moreno, lunes 14 marzo 88, 1988 March 14 (Box 18)
- Reunion Familiar - domingo 13 marzo 88, 1988 March 13 (Box 18)
- Ypacarai - domingo 13 marzo 88, 1988 March 13 (Box 18)
- Santa Teresa - lunes 14 marzo 88 #1, 1988 March 14 (Box 18)
- YPOA - martes 15 marzo 88 (Fotos de Enrique Bendana), 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- Santa Teresa - lunes 14 marzo 88 #2, 1988 March 14 (Box 18)
- YPOA - martes 15 marzo 88 (Fotos de Enrique Bendana), 1988 March 15 (Box 18)
- Charleston - Grandchildren - Napa Valley - Vancouver - Baku - China - July 4 - Williamsburg - Carriage Drives, 1986 (Box 19, Box 20)
- J.Y. Ranch 43rd Anniversary Trip, 1998 (Box 19)
- Charleston and Middleton Plantation #2, 1986 April (Box 19)
- Charleston #1, 1986 April (Box 19)
- Untitled, 1986 (Box 19)
- XV Dartmouth Conference, Baku and Shaki, USSR, 1986 May 13-16 (Box 19)
- San Francisco, Napa Valley, Vancouver, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #1, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #2, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #3, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #4, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #5, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #6, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #7, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #8, 1986 July 4 (Box 19)
- On board the Highlander #9; President Reagan's departure from Kykuit, 1986 July 5 (Box 19)
- Untitled, 1986 August (Box 19)
- State Planning Commission (Box 20)
- Beijing Jeep Corp. (Box 20)
- Ministry of Finance (Box 20)
- Civil Aviation Administration of China (Box 20)
- Chase fifth anniversary reception (Box 20)
- Chase Beijing Office (Box 20)
- Bank of China (Box 20)
- People's Bank of China (Box 20)
- Civil Aviation Administration of China (Box 20)
- Ministry of Finance (Box 20)
- Ministry of Foreign Economic Relations and Trade (Box 20)
- Ministry of Petroleum Industry (Box 20)
- Beijing Municipal Government (Box 20)
- Huaneng (Box 20)
- State Planning Commission (Box 20)
- Beijing Jeep Corp. (Box 20)
- Dartmouth XV (Box 20)
- Loose, untitled photographs (Box 20)
- Chase Beijing office (Box 20)
- Bank of China (Box 20)
- Bob and Linda Douglass with PR and puppy, 1986 May 30 (Box 20)
- Chase fifth anniversary reception (Box 20)
- Huaneng Corp. (Box 20)
- Ministry of Petroleum Industry (Box 20)
- People's Bank of China (Box 20)
- Ministry of Foreign Economic Relations and Trade (Box 20)
- Beijing Municipal Government (Box 20)
- St. Barts - Seal Harbor - Cruise with K - Galapagos Islands - Spain - Cleveland (Grandfather's Grave) - JY Ranch, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Box 22)
- St. Barts, 1986 (Box 21)
- St. Barts, 1987 March 20-23 (Box 21)
- St. Barts, Thanksgiving, 1986 November (Box 21)
- Eileen, Paul, Adam - PR and DR, 1986 (Box 21)
- Family Polaroids (Box 21)
- Ringing Point, 1986 (Box 21)
- Quito, Ecuador, Galapagos Islands #1, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Sleepy Hollow Restoration trip up the Hudson on the Intrepid; Galapagos Islands, Ecuador, 1986 October-1987 February (Box 21)
- Galapagos Islands #3, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Galapagos Islands #4, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Galapagos Islands #5, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Galapagos Islands #6, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Galapagos Islands #7, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Galapagos Islands #8, 1987 February (Box 21)
- Pocantico (Box 22)
- Siguenza, Spain, 1987 March 7-8 (Box 22)
- Plane (Box 22)
- Siguenza, Spain, 1987 March 7-8 (Box 22)
- Visit to Grandfather Rockefeller's grave, Lake View Cemetery, Cleveland Ohio, 1987 May 2-3 (Box 22)
- Carriage Drive at Pocantico; Peggy's garden, Pocantico, 1987 May (Box 22)
- Visit to the Clum Cottage in Irvington with the Hobes and cruise from Kingston to Saugerties on a 34' sloop with Eilene, 1987 June (Box 22)
- Jackson Hole, DR Jr. and DR Sr., 1989 June (Box 22)
- Trip to J.Y. Valley ranch, 1987 June 17-22 (Box 22)
- Bangkok, 1987 (Box 22)
- Carlsberg Castle near Copenhagen, Denmark; Palace of the Emerald Buddha, Bangkok, Thailand #1, 1987 November (Box 22)
- Palace of the Emerald Buddha, Bangkok, Thailand; "Look Out" in Hong Kong, China; Melbourne, Australia, 1987 November (Box 22)
- Buddha Island, 1987 August (Box 22)
- Cruise to Canada, Visit to Livingston and the Stone House Farm with Laurence and Mary R., 1987 August-1987 October (Box 22)
- Cruise, 1987 August (Box 22)
- Cruise to Endfort and Canada, pictures taken by PR, 1987 August (Box 23)
- Cruise with Rick Solomon; Peter Lindquist's wedding, Seal Harbor, 1987 June-July (Box 23)
- Peter Lindquist's wedding in Seal Harbor, Cruise with Adam, 1987 July (Box 23)
- Autumn colors on the carriage drive, Seal Harbor, 1987 October 12 (Box 23)
- Autumn colors on the carriage drive, Seal Harbor, 1987 October 12 (Box 23)
- Picnic on Island with Clayton R., Cruise to Rogue Island, 1987 August (Box 23)
- Cattle auction at the farm barns, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- The cattle auction at Pocantico; The Pappalando family; Last cruise on Jack Tar II, 1987 October 5-10 (Box 23)
- Cattle sale at Pocantico, photos taken by Pappalando family from Paraguay, 1987 (Box 23)
- Pappalando family pictures of the Cattle sale and visit to Kykuit and Hudson Pines, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Cattle sale at the farm barns, Pocantico - photos taken by Luis, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Pocantico - cattle and gardens at Kykuit, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Pictures of Kykuit - visit by the Pappalando family at the time of the cattle auction, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Pictures taken by Luis of Kykuit, the Playhouse; Hudson Pines at time of cattle sale, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Reception at Kykuit and drive at Coach barn before the cattle auction - taken by Luis, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Coach barns - old cam.; Hudson Pine barns taken at the time of the cattle auction by Luis, 1987 October 5 (Box 23)
- Views of Ocean View Farm #3, 1987 November (Box 23)
- Ocean View Farm and Middle Island - Australia #4 (Box 23)
- Sheep on Ocean View Farm, Visit to Middle Island - Australia #5, 1987 November (Box 23)
- Hudson Pines Xmas party at the Playhouse, 1987 December (Box 23)
- Spring Moon coming out of the mold, Seal Harbor; Standing on Long Pond, 1987 December (Box 23)
- Jackson Hole trip in the Teton Wilderness area, 1988 July 1-11 (Box 23)
- Staff Christmas party; Spring Moon still in the mold at Hinkley's, 1987 December (Box 23)
- Pack trip in the Teton Wilderness area, Raft trip and fishing on the Snake River - Jackson Hole, 1988 July (Box 24)
- Launching of the Spring Moon at Hinckley's boat yard, Our first cruise to Buddle Island - Seal Harbor, 1988 July 15 (Box 24)
- Thai event, 1988 April 20 (Box 24)
- Loose photos (Box 24)
- Seal Harbor - Launching of the Spring Moon, Visit of Roberto Ceasar, MCHT picture on Round Island, Cruise, 1988 July-August (Box 24)
- Loose photos (Box 24)
- Launching of the Spring Moon at Hinckley's, Seal Harbor, 1988 July-August (Box 24)
- Loose photo (Box 24)
- Visit to Tokyo branch of Chase with Robert Binney, County Manager, 1988 April (Box 24)
- Picture of Ocean View Farm taken by T. Moore, Australia, 1987 (Box 24)
- San Francisco - Bill H's new home in Napa Valley; Seal Harbor - Bartlett's Island, 1988 July-August (Box 24)
- Cruise with Peggy and Danny on the Spring Moon, Christmas Cove, Monhegan Island, Seal Harbor, 1988 August-September (Box 24)
- Tarrytown - Our 48th wedding anniversary dinner at Hudson Pines, The new house under construction, 1988 September-October (Box 24)
- Last cruise of the year on Spring Moon, Carriage drive - Columbus Day weekend, Seal Harbor #1, 1988 October 6-10 (Box 24)
- Puebla, Mexico - Popocatepetl Volcano, 1988 November (Box 24)